FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Biryulka, Host, Zinger, Hazelnut
How did I become
queen
All characters are fictitious
and the events shown are fiction.
Episode 19
AZALEA
Who are you?
What did you do to Soyeon?
Let go!
Answer if you want to live.
I didn't do anything.
I just opened my eyes and found myself in the body of this woman.
Where is the real Soyeon?
I don't know.
I don't know if she's alive or dead.
I'll kill you.
Benin.
How long have you been in Soyeon's body?
From the day I woke up after falling into the lake.
You said you know everything about me and Soyeon.
All of her memories suddenly came back to me.
There you are.
Get up
unless you want to die here.
Hold my hand until we get out of here.
-What are you planning?
-If there are her memories,
That means Seoyeon is still inside you.
Try to survive.
You must survive.
I knew it.
The woman you're in love with...
Stop it.
I don't want to harm you, get out of our way.
How self-confident!
Take them!
The Minister of War disobeyed the order!
From now on, I give the orders!
-Eat!
Get up, get up.
You're bleeding heavily.
We need to stop him.
What is this?
This is a list of conspirators.
Protect yourself with it.
Do you remember how we played hide and seek as children?
I'll count to 10
and you will hide.
Let's go together.
He's stalking us.
It's pointless.
Go.
And don't look back.
No.
Save Soyeon.
Live up.
I count to 10.
1, 2, 3...
5, 6...
Who sent you?
Who else?
Your father.
9, 10.
I tried not to look back.
For the queen!
Benin.
Come here. Let's take a walk together.
When I first meet the king, I will pin up my hair.
Can you help me choose a hairpin?
She doesn't have to be fancy
I don’t want the regular one either.
Look ahead.
I
always looked at you.
I saw you like this
what you didn't know yourself to be.
Why...
Why me
don't understand?
She didn't go far. Find her!
Where did she go?
Search everywhere!
-Eat!
Over there!
What should I do alone with this thing?
I don't even know where I am.
What can I do?
I couldn't do anything when people were dying before my eyes!
Nothing!
This is the end.
No matter how hard I try,
some things are not meant to happen.
OK. Take me away.
It's all over anyway.
The man who rose from the dead
Queen.
You're alive.
I'm glad.
I'm very happy.
Everything will be fine.
You're alive, everything will be fine.
That's all I need.
Everyone died.
Lady Choi,
Hong Young and Kim Byungin.
Everyone died.
Kim Byungin is dead?
He died because of me.
Everyone died because of me.
Calm down.
My queen, calm down.
Hong Young and Lady Choi
alive.
Your Majesty!
Hong Young!
Your Majesty.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Where is Lady Choi?
Your Majesty!
Court lady Choi.
-Oh no. Lady Choi.
-Your Majesty.
As expected, it is dangerous outside the palace.
It probably hurts.
It hurts like crazy.
How so.
God.
Don't worry
it means I won't die.
With a mortal wound, I would not feel pain.
But he swung his sword.
Let's say I'm lucky.
Back!
He didn't wield a sword well, and that also saved him.
I really thought something happened to you!
Your Majesty.
Sorry. I didn't want to.
-Everything is fine?
-Yes.
I'm sorry.
Where have you been, Your Majesty?
I searched the whole forest.
But I couldn't find it.
A lot of people were looking for you.
But the king found you.
-Your Majesty.
-We missed you.
I'm so glad you're safe.
God.
Needs to be washed.
You're pregnant.
Why did you go into the forest?
You didn't come back for a long time.
I followed you.
You always surprise me.
There was no choice.
Without you in the palace
it was like an eclipse.
Everywhere I went there was darkness.
Come on
I’ll explain what an eclipse is.
No need to explain. I know everything.
I felt the same way.
I missed you.
The pain in my soul was stronger
body pain from wounds.
I won't leave you alone again.
Sorry.
-Are you seriously injured?
-I'm fine.
With the medications I'll be as good as new.
Did you find out who attacked you?
I saw a familiar face.
Donghak followers!
I saw the king.
The king is alive.
Stop.
A state of emergency has been declared.
How dare a woman walk around alone?
Cho's rejected concubine.
I'm ashamed to appear in public
I wanted to get some fresh air while no one was there.
It's dangerous on the streets now. Go back.
I understood. Thank you.
The greedy Kim clan tried to kill the king
and frame the innocent.
Fate decided to leave the king alive.
Is it possible to occupy a throne that is already occupied?
The king is alive.
Mister!
It was on the streets, sir.
What is there to make so much noise?
God.
The king is alive.
If so, then the queen
I didn’t leave to recover.
So,
Kim Jwageun saw right through Kim Byongin.
I can’t believe that he foresaw Benin’s betrayal.
The gentleman wants us to remain silent about the death of Benin.
-Yes, father.
-However,
We have now established relations with Jvagyn.
But they missed the queen.
We have to try
make amends, right?
That's it! If you boil it so much, it will completely soften.
Leave him alone.
After the queen left to recuperate,
he lost his mind.
They say that hatred makes you more deeply attached than love.
I think he became very attached to her while she was here.
I can't believe the king died in vain.
He truly cared about his people.
As expected, you are alone here.
Yes, no one is waiting for me at home.
Is Her Majesty also very depressed?
I don’t even know what to tell you, court lady Choi.
Your very existence
has already comforted and reassured me.
I even forgot about the complaints for a while.
I feel the same thanks to you.
Do you want to eat?
No, thanks.
I'm a little busy.
Just a minute. I have something to give you.
I like you.
I love you.
I'm not in a position to express
these feelings so
you should
meet a good woman
to brighten up your loneliness.
Court lady Choi.
I felt that something was wrong.
How's the cooking going?
Oh no!
Royal Chef!
Oh, I ruined everything.
It's a rare sight to see a royal chef spoil food.
What happened to you?
Nothing wrong with me. Something happened to the country.
Panic gripped the south of the country.
So in the last days there are no gifts.
Royal chef.
I heard that strange proclamations were posted on the streets of the city.
Those who attacked the king...
If not the followers of Tonhak, who else would do such a thing?
They all need to be executed. Catch and kill!
Kill? Do you even know how to do this?
So shut your mouth.
Tell me about it.
I've worn it too long. I started to get tired.
I think it's time to take it off.
Can you handle it? You worked with me for 10 years.
What?
Where are you going?
Who will cook?
There are many in Joseon who can be royal chefs.
What's happening?
In recent days, strange appeals have appeared on the streets of the city.
They say we are talking about rumors about the king.
Here's how.
Are rumors important now?
It will all be over after the coronation.
What should we worry about now?
so this is the letter on which our lives depend.
It's suspicious that Kim Byungin is nowhere to be seen these days.
The Queen left to prepare for the birth.
And Kim Byungin is missing too?
Death of the King and Departure of the Queen.
Everything is somehow suspicious.
What if both are lies?
He hid the queen
who considers the king's death imaginary,
and took her side?
Then Kim Byongin signed the letter,
to destroy the Kim clan.
Cold.
Cold?
How awkward.
Wait a minute.
As soon as you left, it suddenly got colder.
Are you cold because I wasn't around?
Thank you for your boundless love.
2, 3, 1, 1, 2, 3,
2, 1, 2, 3,
- 4, 1, 2, 3, 4.
-Continue.
This is...
The training you talked about.
So that's why you wrote a textbook on military tactics.
I can't believe that the king is a follower of donghak.
I even hid it from them.
Like a merchant, dissatisfied with the country that helps him.
Why are you doing such dangerous things?
They say the enemy of your enemy is your friend.
Corrupt officials are our common enemy.
Isn't the scope too small?
Where is everyone?
Do you want us to get together and kill us all at once?
Everyone will come together at the right time.
In the meantime, it's safer to be apart!
Are you in charge here?
Yes, I am.
1, 2, 3. Four.
1, 2, 3. Five.
1, 2, 3. Six.
1, 2, 3. Seven.
-1, 2, 3. Eight.
-Nice to meet you.
It's clear from your face that you're in charge.
The scar on the eye is especially impressive.
Nice to meet you.
The main thing here is the one who lives longer.
As soon as one dies, the next one becomes the main one.
To be in charge means to survive the longest.
If I die, he will become the boss here.
Nine. 1, 2, 3. Ten.
This baby?
I heard you are close with my Damhyang.
My Damhyang?
So you...
He is Damhyang's father, whom we were looking for.
The one whose eye was damaged with a pitchfork?
It's a small world!
If it weren't for Damhyang, I would have already killed this guy.
I'll meet the damn king
who brought the country to this point,
I'll cut his throat right away. That's what I thought.
Thanks to your daughter.
You could have died trying to kill me.
What?
I didn't need to save you.
You just had to finish it off with a straw knife.
3. Ten.
How many more times do we have to repeat this?
You have to feel it for yourself!
Should I say this every time?
Damhyang saved you. And she also saved me.
The king does not abandon his people.
Therefore, the people save the king.
By the way, what happened to the warriors who were chasing me?
Many were born and raised here.
They are hunters and gatherers of herbs.
They know the mountains like the back of their hand.
The guards can't reach them here.
What about the weird guy in the tokkaebi mask?
Did you grab it?
-Wearing a tokkebi mask?
- 1, 2,
3. 1, 2...
Was he chasing you too?
He tried to kill me.
Kim Byungin died
trying to stop him.
Masked Man
serves Kim Jwageun.
Kim Jwageun is back.
1, 2, 3. Seven.
1, 2, 3. Eight.
1, 2, 3. Nine.
1, 2, 3. Ten.
Straight out from Death Note.
Here are the names of all the officials,
which need to be removed.
All that remains is to find a way to return to the palace.
If you gather everyone,
who is on our side, how many can we recruit?
If collected from all over the country,
then about 1000 people.
-That's all?
-That's a lot.
Risking your life is not easy.
Then why didn't they kill the governors?
Get rid of them and you will win the war.
Do you think we are some kind of bloodthirsty hyenas?
Even low-born people like us
united, they can instill fear in the rulers.
This was our intention.
It's clear. So you wanted to attract attention?
This is a good strategy.
You didn't give them a reason to start fighting against you.
Maybe we're stupid
but we knew that if we came face to face, we would lose.
They gathered 1000 warriors.
I risked my life for the sake of the country!
Do you think I'm up to something?
-Royal chef?
-Incredible.
Royal chef?
How can we trust the man from the palace?
Well, of course.
Fine. I'll come back. Untie me.
OK. I'll untie it myself.
Why are you looking so angry?
You are definitely younger than me. Where are your manners?
If you beg, I won’t stay!
Out of the way!
You came of your own accord,
but you won’t be able to leave like that.
Some familiar situation.
You've seen all our faces.
And they even found out about this place.
Do you think you can leave alive?
What?
There you go.
Damn it. No need.
Royal chef.
It seems my time has come. You'll hear something like this.
Manbok.
Your Majesty! Why are you...
Your Majesty!
Royal Chef!
Court Lady Choi!
Court lady Choi.
-Royal cook.
-Court Lady Choi.
What's happened?
Who did it?
What is this?
-Royal cook.
-I knew that you would save me.
What brought you here?
Your Majesty.
I heard that everyone who was unhappy in this country came here.
So I went myself.
And the people who disappeared from the palace are also here.
Royal Chef, were you unhappy in this country?
Watching what's going on in the palace,
even I, the happiest of all, became unhappy.
What's going on in the palace?
About this, Your Majesty.
Change your clothes first.
And cover yourself when you sneeze.
Tomorrow is the coronation ceremony.
Every second counts.
You did a good job.
By the way, why are the followers of donghak
Are they resisting more and more, because we have reined them in?
Bad news is reaching me.
The point is, the more your opponent retreats,
the more you justify yourself and act more violently.
Therefore, the only solution is to teach them a tougher lesson.
After the ceremony
I'll use the guns to take back control.
I haven't seen you with a sword for a long time.
Is the palace no longer safe?
This is a gift from the Queen.
-Queens?
-In fact,
I'm afraid I have bad news for you.
Benin sacrificed himself
to save the queen.
That's how it is.
The only drawback of youth is stupidity:
sacrifice everything for fleeting feelings.
So the queen survived?
Yes.
The queen was saved by the king.
So, does that mean they're both alive?
This makes you think:
there is no one to rely on, or are they that smart?
I'm sorry. Therefore...
That time we tried
give the queen arsenic,
the king found out about this and came running.
I think
there was a rat who had been listening all this time.
It was you who gave it to me as a gift.
You personally blinded and stunned her.
I'm overly sensitive
apparently because of the upcoming ceremony.
I understand everything.
We will hold the ceremony as soon as possible.
Don't forget that those two already defeated you once.
I'll bet my life
for this fight.
I have an idea.
We will be able to pass the gates at Hanyang and the palace.
So what did you come up with?
These people are accustomed to eating fresh food.
How long will they last without fresh food?
The Queen Dowager is extremely picky.
She won't last long.
Not this.
That.
Therefore
this door will not be closed under any circumstances.
Products are delivered through it.
We need to find out about the royal offering cart.
The palace has a whole system for royal offerings.
More than 50 such carts come to the royal kitchen every day.
Moreover, there are special monthly offerings.
And there are also offerings that come every 4 months.
-Simpler. Straight to the point.
-Fine.
62 carts will arrive at the palace
on the morning of the ceremony.
But a state of emergency has been declared.
I am sure that the royal offerings will be checked with special attention.
But what if there is a cart that no one knows about?
Inspector's carriage.
Well, you're finally here.
This cart is ours. Skip them.
-Fine. Come on in.
-Yes.
Chief Inspector
usually swaps carts.
Swaps?
Well, not all officials are picky.
He changes some of the offerings
for slightly lower quality products.
And in the inspector's cart lie
products for which he exchanges offerings.
And only a handful of people know about it.
I knew it.
This is not a palace, but a den of thieves.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was necessary.
Rotten wood has holes.
And we can use them.
So, let's all hold out our hands.
-Let's.
-All?
Hands here. Forward.
-Here.
-God.
1, 2, 3.
Go ahead!
-Forward!
Forward.
-Ready?
-Yes, let's go.
-Manbok.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Faster.
-And he has changed.
-Let's go.
Thank you
and forgive me.
You were special to Kim Soyeon too.
I want to bury him myself.
Fine.
Rest in peace.
Shall we go?
Speak.
The Queen must prepare for the birth of her baby
with mother
but since this is impossible, I would like to help her myself.
Came to ask where she was.
The Queen bears an heir, so
I can’t tell you its location.
I provided her with everything she needed,
so don't worry.
Here.
The king is not dead
Is she really getting ready to give birth?
You didn't harm her, did you?
The queen has escaped.
We defend her honor.
-Run away?
-She believes
that the king is alive, she even left the palace.
I'm sorry,
but I will tell you openly, Your Majesty.
Your behavior doesn't help our family,
but on the contrary, it tarnishes her name.
Don't you understand
what will our future generation say about us?
Are you in a position to talk like that?
At least I have a feeling of shame.
Your shame is your crime.
If there is no shame, there is no crime.
If not for the sake of family honor,
then why did you come so far?
Even the king was harmed.
My time won't end
until I want it myself.
You hear everything.
-There.
-Teho.
Your Majesty.
They got there before us.
-Yes.
God, my knees hurt so much.
Your Majesty.
Hello.
Glad you're alive.
You've been through a lot.
We're glad you're safe.
Who has cigarettes?
Your Majesty, it's cold here.
I wouldn't mind a cold can of beer right now.
It's not so great here
so why did we come?
It's safest here
no one knows about this place.
How's that? Even if you want it, you won't find it.
God, my legs.
Crap.
It's not time yet.
How long is it possible?
This is the last chance. You need to be careful.
It's already time.
So delicious?
-Here.
God.
Very tasty.
Looking for trouble?
People like me will still die
We have no choice.
And you have the highest position in all of Joseon.
If we closed our eyes to everything, wouldn’t we live in abundance?
There was a time when I
lived in a nightmare that I had to endure.
I endured everything only with the thought of taking revenge on those
who killed my parents, brothers and sisters.
Then began to see the rotting of Joseon
and people who suffered.
And you have a keen eye.
I thought that everyone in the palace was blind.
If everything works out,
You won't become like them, will you?
I
I dream of a new Joseon.
You called it "elections"?
What?
When people choose their king.
Yes. Elections.
But this does not mean that the world will become ideal.
Well, that's already good.
You can change it if something goes wrong.
Both the king and the queen are both madmen.
Well, go to bed early, we have a big deal ahead of us.
Good night.
If you really are from the future,
it means you know how it will all end.
What will happen?
You will lose.
But I'll bet everything on you.
Aren't you always on the winning side?
Nothing.
I've already screwed up in this life.
Even if I put everything on the line, it’s okay.
So you put all your eggs in my basket?
Yes. All. I went all in.
Even if I fail, I will do my best.
Until fate gets tired of me,
I won’t let her eat me up so easily.
I can't believe it
that I'm stuck here and can't help the king.
Do you think the queen met him?
Even if they met, what can they do on their own?
I don't think there is
way to stop the coronation.
And if you use Kim Hwan...
Hon.
Have you come again?
Brought something.
What is this?
I'm collecting requests
to free you.
But is there anything else I can do to help?
Help?
Yes. Ask for anything.
-All?
-Yes.
I'll do anything for you.
Why
do you trust people that much?
Is your job to feed scammers?
How are you going to survive in this cruel world?
Sorry, I was wrong.
-What is wrong?
-I don’t know what exactly,
but since you say so, I won’t do it anymore.
You're wrong about that
that you trust people like me.
I tried to be friends with you
to find out information.
And you had no idea.
What's all this for?
That is
all this time you didn't consider me a friend?
No.
I didn't count you
your friend not for a second.
So don't you dare come back.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Blame it on
can't we use it anymore?
I didn't look at you.
Now before my eyes
such a dishonor has happened.
You must be very tired.
I don't dilute with water.
I mix it with soju.
Golden ratio, somek.
You seem to be dreaming about something good.
What a relief.
What did you dream about?
The king's portrait was blazing.
The fire consumed all of Seongwonjong.
And I'm stuck here alone when the fire...
Today is a significant day.
Not a drop can be spilled.
Powder me so that I don't have a single blemish.
Day of the accession ceremony
For Your Majesty's safety
I ordered a curfew in the palace.
Everyone except the warriors
must remain inside the palace.
Yes.
I didn't invite the royal family, nor did I invite the musicians.
Let the ceremony proceed peacefully.
Even the royal family?
It will be safer this way.
But...
Everything I say is correct.
I understand.
Your Majesty, aren't you scared?
Don't worry.
The believers I sometimes met on the street
they said that my ancestors would give me a blessing.
So I'll use it now.
Your Majesty,
today more than any other day,
you look like the queen I know.
There is no need for such a mood.
It's like the last day.
And this is just the beginning.
You are right, Your Majesty.
Meet us at the palace at night.
Certainly. It's time to go.
Don't die.
What's so good in life?
Even if our life is miserable
and it’s a pity, let’s live longer.
If everything works out now,
I'll "vote" for you, or whatever it is,
in place of the king.
Thank you.
Well, shall we go?
It's time to go home.
Criminal Lee Kyung-eun
hid the identities of the traitors, the followers of donghak.
He will be stripped of his position
and sent into exile.
Criminal Hong Duil
lost a firearm.
He will work in the office
Ganghwa within 600 days
like a state slave.
After the ascension ceremony
I will carry out the sentence immediately.
There were no achievements to
attribute something to the current king.
It wasn't easy for us.
The king's funeral service is not over yet.
Is it appropriate to smile to your teeth?
I'm sorry.
How will the ceremony go, will there be any problems -
it's all up to you.
Yes! I will definitely do my duty
so that the absence of the Minister of War
didn't affect anything.
By the way,
When will Kim Byungin return to the palace?
I suppose you want to know the fate of the letter.
Everyone is worried about it.
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
Yes, yes.
Now the king and the Phunyang family of Cho
will be my puppets.
Sir, I pay double for the palace.
Doubly.
Hey, we're good people.
But if the Chief Inspector or anyone
he still sees something suspicious,
we can actually become bad.
I don't care
whether human nature is good or not.
It all depends on what they do.
Be more natural, more natural.
Let's.
Let's go.
It's uncomfortable, move a little.
Like this?
Is this an elbow?
Hare poke at me.
If you put pressure on my stomach like that...
That's it.
Move over.
Oh you.
Finally I see something.
Right here...
There is no time for this.
You're right, you need to pull yourself together.
It's good that I didn't hide here
with some guard.
Why are you talking about this?
Move a little, I’ll change my position.
Mommies.
Now I'm comfortable.
I agree, this pose is the best.
We will be caught because of the roar of your heart.
Why are you so scared?
It's not just my heart.
And not only because of fear.
It's also because of you, my queen.
For me, it’s not out of fear either.
It's from England.
Much more powerful and faster.
If the king appears in the palace,
aim for his heart.
New, or what?
Yes.
Come on in.
Stop.
-Search.
-Yes!
Nothing suspicious.
How I became queen
As soon as the ceremony is over,
I will finish them all off.
Same feeling as before
the appearance of the main boss in the games.
I'm good with knives.
I'm crazy.
From words about a special task
My heart began to boil.
The changes you feared have already begun.
What the hell are you doing?
Is the king on the same side as the donghak followers?
I am a relative of those you killed.
I am the king of those people whom you have neglected!